[
  {
    "question": "dies",
    "answer": "αυτό",
    "phonetic": "af**TÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "nicht",
    "answer": "όχι",
    "phonetic": "**Ó**chi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Problem",
    "answer": "πρόβλημα",
    "phonetic": "**PRÓ**vlima"
  },
  {
    "question": "helfen",
    "answer": "βοηθάω",
    "phonetic": "voï**THÁ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "offen",
    "answer": "ανοιχτό",
    "phonetic": "ani**CHTÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "geschlossen",
    "answer": "κλειστό",
    "phonetic": "kli**STÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaputt",
    "answer": "χαλασμένο",
    "phonetic": "chala**SMÉ**no"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaufen",
    "answer": "αγοράζω",
    "phonetic": "agho**RÁ**zo"
  },
  {
    "question": "sprechen",
    "answer": "μιλάω",
    "phonetic": "mi**LÁ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "bitte",
    "answer": "παρακαλώ",
    "phonetic": "paraka**LÓ**"
  }
]